[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brighton", "Summerville", "Cambridge", "New York City"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "At what stage does he get away from them?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "stage", "does", "he", "get", "away", "from", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, they go from Brighton to Summerville to Cambridge looking for gasoline because apparently there was this plan cooked up to go to New York City and the tank only had about a quarter full.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "go", "from", "Brighton", "to", "Summerville", "to", "Cambridge", "looking", "for", "gasoline", "because", "apparently", "there", "was", "this", "plan", "cooked", "up", "to", "go", "to", "New", "York", "City", "and", "the", "tank", "only", "had", "about", "a", "quarter", "full", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What was his account of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "his", "account", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "This is entitled to a complete independent investigation, as opposed to any kind of partisan charges back and forth, because this is very, very serious, that we didn't identify this man properly is something that we shouldn't allow to happen in the future.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "entitled", "to", "a", "complete", "independent", "investigation", ",", "as", "opposed", "to", "any", "kind", "of", "partisan", "charges", "back", "and", "forth", ",", "because", "this", "is", "very", ",", "very", "serious", ",", "that", "we", "did", "n't", "identify", "this", "man", "properly", "is", "something", "that", "we", "should", "n't", "allow", "to", "happen", "in", "the", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Is that where you think the secret of all this really lies?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "where", "you", "think", "the", "secret", "of", "all", "this", "really", "lies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I would think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Graham"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "What can Americans do to secure itself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "Americans", "do", "to", "secure", "itself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNPS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "As Senator Graham said, America needs to step up its game.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "Senator", "Graham", "said", ",", "America", "needs", "to", "step", "up", "its", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Boylston Street"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Where were you when these bombs went off?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "these", "bombs", "went", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "We were on Boylston Street, not far from the finish line, and after looking at the photos that I've seen from that day, we were probably only three or four feet from where the first bomb went off.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "on", "Boylston", "Street", ",", "not", "far", "from", "the", "finish", "line", ",", "and", "after", "looking", "at", "the", "photos", "that", "I", "'ve", "seen", "from", "that", "day", ",", "we", "were", "probably", "only", "three", "or", "four", "feet", "from", "where", "the", "first", "bomb", "went", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kaitlynn"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "And what was your instant reaction after they had gone off?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "instant", "reaction", "after", "they", "had", "gone", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, after the first bomb went off, we were knocked to the ground and my first reaction I guess maybe I watch too much TV, my first reaction was to climb on top of Kaitlynn and I was yelling at her to stay down.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "after", "the", "first", "bomb", "went", "off", ",", "we", "were", "knocked", "to", "the", "ground", "and", "my", "first", "reaction", "I", "guess", "maybe", "I", "watch", "too", "much", "TV", ",", "my", "first", "reaction", "was", "to", "climb", "on", "top", "of", "Kaitlynn", "and", "I", "was", "yelling", "at", "her", "to", "stay", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Was it the first or second blast you think that caused her injuries?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "the", "first", "or", "second", "blast", "you", "think", "that", "caused", "her", "injuries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "It was the first blast.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "the", "first", "blast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "You were so fast in the action that you took that actually the doctors at the hospital were not even aware there had been a major incident, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "so", "fast", "in", "the", "action", "that", "you", "took", "that", "actually", "the", "doctors", "at", "the", "hospital", "were", "not", "even", "aware", "there", "had", "been", "a", "major", "incident", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "EX", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "I don't know that nobody at the hospital was aware, but when we pulled up, you know, I came sort of speeding into the area outside of the emergency room and we told those people outside the door, the ambassadors that helped get us into emergency, that a bomb had gone off and we told the people that we first came in contact with in the emergency room that she was injured in the bombing and they had no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "nobody", "at", "the", "hospital", "was", "aware", ",", "but", "when", "we", "pulled", "up", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "came", "sort", "of", "speeding", "into", "the", "area", "outside", "of", "the", "emergency", "room", "and", "we", "told", "those", "people", "outside", "the", "door", ",", "the", "ambassadors", "that", "helped", "get", "us", "into", "emergency", ",", "that", "a", "bomb", "had", "gone", "off", "and", "we", "told", "the", "people", "that", "we", "first", "came", "in", "contact", "with", "in", "the", "emergency", "room", "that", "she", "was", "injured", "in", "the", "bombing", "and", "they", "had", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What was the first thing that you did?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "first", "thing", "that", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, actually I wasn't running when they went off.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", "I", "was", "n't", "running", "when", "they", "went", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "When you got to the hospital and you saw the kind of injuries coming in, was this reminiscent to you of a battle zone?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "got", "to", "the", "hospital", "and", "you", "saw", "the", "kind", "of", "injuries", "coming", "in", ",", "was", "this", "reminiscent", "to", "you", "of", "a", "battle", "zone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Unfortunately, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leo"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Did you actually have anything to do with Kaitlynn at all during her time there?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "actually", "have", "anything", "to", "do", "with", "Kaitlynn", "at", "all", "during", "her", "time", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "So I have to -- I have to correct Leo in only the nicest way, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "have", "to", "--", "I", "have", "to", "correct", "Leo", "in", "only", "the", "nicest", "way", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kaitlynn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "In terms of the speed with which Leo managed to get Kaitlynn to the hospital, would that have played a significant effect perhaps on saving her leg if not her life?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "speed", "with", "which", "Leo", "managed", "to", "get", "Kaitlynn", "to", "the", "hospital", ",", "would", "that", "have", "played", "a", "significant", "effect", "perhaps", "on", "saving", "her", "leg", "if", "not", "her", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "There is -- there is no doubt that the time -- the time from injury to surgical intervention, particularly for bleeding wounds, is a key factor in preventing greater disability, loss of limb and loss of life.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "--", "there", "is", "no", "doubt", "that", "the", "time", "--", "the", "time", "from", "injury", "to", "surgical", "intervention", ",", "particularly", "for", "bleeding", "wounds", ",", "is", "a", "key", "factor", "in", "preventing", "greater", "disability", ",", "loss", "of", "limb", "and", "loss", "of", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leo", "Kaitlynn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Walter Reed"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What did he have to say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "have", "to", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, you know, to the room, there were some other victims and their families and friends there and to the room, he delivered what was a very inspirational speech, if you will, about seeing people who were victims of these type of injuries at Walter Reed in his visits there, and in monitoring their recovery and seeing them all, you know, recover fully or get better.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "to", "the", "room", ",", "there", "were", "some", "other", "victims", "and", "their", "families", "and", "friends", "there", "and", "to", "the", "room", ",", "he", "delivered", "what", "was", "a", "very", "inspirational", "speech", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "about", "seeing", "people", "who", "were", "victims", "of", "these", "type", "of", "injuries", "at", "Walter", "Reed", "in", "his", "visits", "there", ",", "and", "in", "monitoring", "their", "recovery", "and", "seeing", "them", "all", ",", "you", "know", ",", "recover", "fully", "or", "get", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Finally, L, how is Kaitlynn doing?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "L", ",", "how", "is", "Kaitlynn", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "She's doing better.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "doing", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Did you hear them live or were you watching somewhere?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "hear", "them", "live", "or", "were", "you", "watching", "somewhere", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I just missed the bombs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "missed", "the", "bombs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What made you do it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "You know, it's about when I was there in Boston, you know, after the tragedy happened, you saw how the community came together.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "when", "I", "was", "there", "in", "Boston", ",", "you", "know", ",", "after", "the", "tragedy", "happened", ",", "you", "saw", "how", "the", "community", "came", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "When you heard that these two bomb suspects were ethnic Chechens, went what went through mind?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "that", "these", "two", "bomb", "suspects", "were", "ethnic", "Chechens", ",", "went", "what", "went", "through", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "You know, what went through my mind is it could have been anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "what", "went", "through", "my", "mind", "is", "it", "could", "have", "been", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Are you feeling confident?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "feeling", "confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I'm feeling confident.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "feeling", "confident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "What is your reflective thought on the last fortnight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reflective", "thought", "on", "the", "last", "fortnight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "There's been so much to digest, so much to comprehend of the themselves, not even thinking about the photography.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "been", "so", "much", "to", "digest", ",", "so", "much", "to", "comprehend", "of", "the", "themselves", ",", "not", "even", "thinking", "about", "the", "photography", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "The fact that people could actually see the horror, firsthand?", "question_tokens": ["The", "fact", "that", "people", "could", "actually", "see", "the", "horror", ",", "firsthand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I think it put a face on this -- it put a face on news bombings.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "put", "a", "face", "on", "this", "--", "it", "put", "a", "face", "on", "news", "bombings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Marine"]}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "And of all of the images you took, so many powerful images, which of the ones stand out for you in your mind?", "question_tokens": ["And", "of", "all", "of", "the", "images", "you", "took", ",", "so", "many", "powerful", "images", ",", "which", "of", "the", "ones", "stand", "out", "for", "you", "in", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "There's a photo that I keep looking back at and it's a picture of a Marine.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "photo", "that", "I", "keep", "looking", "back", "at", "and", "it", "'s", "a", "picture", "of", "a", "Marine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "And, John, you left something at the memorial site, I believe?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "John", ",", "you", "left", "something", "at", "the", "memorial", "site", ",", "I", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I went to the memorial site and I saw the three crosses there for the three victims.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "went", "to", "the", "memorial", "site", "and", "I", "saw", "the", "three", "crosses", "there", "for", "the", "three", "victims", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP"], "qSentId": 478, "question": "You guys ready?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Yes!", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Did you just find a basketball?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "just", "find", "a", "basketball", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "It's yours.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "yours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]